To configure auto and raw melt for your Windows 10 or Windows 11 device, we need to create a GPU that will allow all of our devices to auto and roll into mobile device management at your MDM without the users interference.
So what you need to do right now is I'm going to create a GPU in the Europe organizational units, I'm going to create this GPU and just call this.
And the raw melt and then click OK, now we need to actually a data policy.
And here we need to go to policies and they want to go to administrative templates and just expand that.
They want to go to Windows components.
So we're going to look for the following called MDM.
So what you're actually interested on is a following enable automatic MDM enrollment using the default Azure AD credentials.
So I'm going to select that.
So I'm going to do just a click enabled.
You can see we're going to use user's credentials.
We can't really use the device credentials but you want to use user's credentials because if they use a log on to the other device with its long name or with its log on name,
that have a Microsoft internal license or to modify the device would be enrolled to Microsoft to your MDM to into click apply.
And then we need to click OK.
So if I go to my Azure Active Directory, you can see on the answer, for example, I have this user's called for tutorial.
Waltz, I did it the follow.
You can see I have to UPN.
So the first one is a document domain which I created and the second one is the one which I added to this domain environment,
which of course allows the user to log on to this environment using the kel global for. Microsoft.com,
which of course has a license with Microsoft Intune.
And automatically when this user's log on, when I actually configured my Azure AD sync, if I go to my Microsoft Intune,
you can see that the users are already been.
The other already be synced to Microsoft 365, which of course I've already assigned a license to the user, Victoria, John.
So let's go to our Windows 10 device.
I'm going to go to the C002.
And on this device, I actually let me just close this.
So these are Windows 10 device.
And if I go to my start menu, you can see that the user has log on its Victoria, John.
So what I need to do right now is to start the CMD and let us wait for some seconds for the command prompt to start.
Here we go, here we have the command prompt.
So I'm going to enter the following GP updates, and then slash false.
So by the GP updates, false is going to actually try to update the policy, the computer policy, and then the user's policy.
So that policy we just applied using the GPU.
We bought some potentially false to this device.
Or you can only restart your device.
By restart your device, every policy will actually be applied to your device.
You can see the same computer policy.
I don't know.
They said, "I just want to start a device, because those are so true that it was distributed to this device."
Which, of course, requires the device to restart.
So I start doing that.
Then you want to also check if the policy has been applied.
What you need to do is to go to task scheduler.
So if I go to my search and I enter task, it was search for task scheduler.
Here you can see we have our task scheduler.
So let's open task scheduler.
So when we open our task scheduler, and then we go to all edges as pandas.
I go to Microsoft, Windows, and then we go to search for enterprise management.
So let's just go down.
Here we have the enterprise MGMT.
You can see it's so folder had just been created recently.
That's actually new.
And now we're going to see a trace of extra information, which is saying login shell created
a romantic client.
And then when we do just a spend that, here you can see it says, "It does have much here,
run it," and you can see it's Microsoft Corporation.
So this is actually going to tell us that this has actually been triggered.
So let me show you next in this video that this device is going to be ready to start a Microsoft Intune,
because we're logged on with a user's name that have the right license to utterly use the Intune.
If not, the device will not be ready to start Intune.
You're going to receive an error message.